nyra.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy | NYRA

This Privacy Policy applies to the New York Racing Association’s (“NYRA”) websites and applications, NYRA.com, NYRA Now and NYRA At The Track (collectively, the “Sites”) This Privacy Policy explains how NYRA protects your privacy and the confidentiality of the information that you provide to NYRA when you use the Sites or any of NYRA’s partners’ or affiliates’ websites, and related products and services. BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THE PRIVACY POLICY, THEN DO NOT USE THE SITES.  

PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION PROVIDED TO OR COLLECTED BY THE SITES

When you register or open an account with any of the Sites on any NYRA-managed website or application, the Sites may collect some or all of the following “Personal Identifiable Information” voluntarily provided by you, such as:

  * Your Name, Address, Date of Birth, phone number and email address;
  * Your Social Security Number; and
  * Your bank and/or credit card account number.

NYRA may collect the following other information about you, such as:

  * Your IP address, device identifier, and browser history on the Sites;
  * Information volunteered by you, such as survey information and/or website registrations, user id and passwords;
  * Purchases made by you on the Sites;
  * Your wagering or funding activity (identified by your account number and name), or
  * If you choose to connect to the Sites through a social network such as Facebook or Twitter, NYRA may collect your profile information.

The Sites will not give out your Personal Identifiable Information to any third party that is not affiliated with NYRA, except as necessary for the operation of the Sites’ normal businesses or as required or permitted by law.

HOW THE SITE USES THIS INFORMATION

We may use your Personal Identifiable Information to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it to NYRA, including, but not limited to, providing updates about NYRA, verifying your identity, to fulfill your wagering or funding activity or process purchases made on the Sites. NYRA reserves the right to use your Personal Identifiable Information in order to ensure that wagering activity on the Sites meets various state and federal laws and other statutory requirements. In addition, from time to time NYRA or its marketing partners may use your Personal Identifiable Information to contact you regarding promotions and marketing offers and other purposes that are generally limited to NYRA’s services. Personal and other information may be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies in response to warrants, subpoenas, statute, or other governmental orders.

You are hereby advised that in the event of a criminal investigation by state or federal authorities or regulatory inquiry, you waive any and all rights to account holder information and data in the Sites’ possession, and you specifically authorize NYRA to disclose said data and information to law enforcement authorities. In this situation, you agree to release NYRA and NYRA’s affiliated companies from any and all liability related to such disclosure, to the fullest extent permissible by law.

From time to time, NYRA may share information NYRA collects about you with third parties, in an aggregate and confidential form only, in order to assist with marketing or other normal business activities. We require these companies to use your personal information only to provide a particular product or service to you or NYRA, and do not authorize them to use your personal information for any other reason.

DATA INTEGRITY

The Sites process Personal Identifiable Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this privacy policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that NYRA only collect, store and process the information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the information NYRA processes is accurate, complete and current, but NYRA depends on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. All information collected by the Sites remains the exclusive property of NYRA.

PERSONALIZED ADVERTISING-THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Like many other websites, the Sites use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies (“cookies”) to enable NYRA to distinguish you from other users of the Sites. The Sites use cookies to tailor and enhance your experience on the Sites, to show you content that you might be interested in, and to display the content according to your preferences. By continuing to browse the Site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that the Sites store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer or device if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer or device’s hard drive. Cookies permit this website to recognize future visits from that computer. Cookies do not damage your system or impair its functioning in any way. Cookies do not contain any personal identifying information and only contain information, such as a user ID, that a website uses to track the pages you have visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. We use cookies to track users’ traffic patterns when you make any requests for the Sites’ services. When you make your request, NYRA may use a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on the Sites. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to allow your browser to show you when a cookie is sent. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the Sites.

Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which NYRA has no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.

We may use third-parties to process purchases, including, but not limited to, gift shop items and ticketing. The Sites may include links to other websites whose privacy practices NYRA does not control. Information you provide on another website is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of that website. These websites may have privacy policies and practices that differ from NYRA’s. We may use third-party advertisers to serve advertisements on the Sites. Our advertisers may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to, among other things, to enable our advertisers to monitor the ads you have viewed on our website.

WHAT WE DO TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY

To ensure website security and network performance, NYRA monitors all inbound and outbound network traffic in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload and change information, or otherwise cause damage or conduct criminal activity. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to our services are strictly prohibited and shall be punishable under applicable state or federal law. Please be advised, however, that the internet and various networking communication mediums are not secure, unless explicitly stated as such, and may be subject to interception or loss which is beyond the control of NYRA. NYRA uses SSL encryption to protect your personal information during your online interactions with NYRA. NYRA’s SSL uses SHA-2 and 2048-bit encryption which ensures server and client authentication through encrypted algorithms, and is the highest industry standard. NYRA utilizes procedures to protect confidential information offline, as well.  NYRA restricts access to your Personal Identifiable Information to employees who need the information to perform a specific task for you or NYRA. NYRA’s employees use password protected logins to access the Sites’ servers to protect against unauthorized access, acquisition, destruction, use, modification or disclosure of information. The servers which hold Personally Identifiable Information are maintained in a locked, secure hosting environment. Your SSNs, bank account and credit card details are all encrypted while saved on our server. 

DO NOT TRACK: Do Not Track (DNT) is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences regarding tracking by advertisers and other third parties. We do not currently respond to DNT signals.

THE SITES’ USERS

The Sites are not intended for children. The Sites will not knowingly collect information from children.

CHANGES

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 28, 2017. NYRA shall periodically review the appropriateness of this Privacy Policy and shall make, at NYRA’s sole discretion, such changes or modifications as may be deemed necessary. Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy will be noted as such on this website and emailed to our customers on file. NYRA’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal information will be governed by the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at that time. Your continued dealings with the Sites or your use of this website subsequent to any changes or modifications to this Privacy Policy will signify your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the changed Privacy Policy. Accordingly, when you use the Sites, you should check the date of this Privacy Policy and review any changes since the last version you reviewed.
